Abhishek Kumar Singh



abhisheksingh007@outlook.in



7667488641



linkedin.com/in/abhishek-kumar-singh-07



http://coderakki.in/

Summary

I am currently working as Software Engineer at Zensar Technologies from June 2019.

I have skillsets in Python, Hadoop, Asp. Net, Oracle, MSSql, and Android. My area of interest is Machine Learning and

Artificial Intelligence. I am doing competitive coding for more than 4 years.

I am a highly motivated and dedicated person towards my career with command over my coding and interpersonal skills.

I have solely completed many regulatory projects.

My colleague and seniors have commended me for my willingness to participate and my dedication to helping out where

possible.

This is Abhishek Kumar Singh...

Experience

zensar Software Engineer

Zensar Technologies Sep 2020 - Present (8 months +)

ZenSár Junior Software Engineer

Zensar Technologies Sep 2019 - Sep 2020 (1 year 1 month)

zensăr Project Trainee

Zensar Technologies Jun 2019 - Sep 2019 (4 months)

Education



🄊 IES s College of Technology, Kalikheda, Ratibad Main Road, Bhopal - 462044

Bachelor of Engineering, Computer Science 2015 - 2019

Subhash Public School

Higher Education, Science 2013 - 2014

Dev Sangha National School

Matriculation, Science 2008 - 2011

Army Public School, Ranchi

Secondary Education , Science 2006 - 2008

Kendriya Vidyalaya Borjhar

Secondary Education , Science 2000 - 2006

Licenses & Certifications

Big Data - Hadoop - KVCH 713198

Android - KVCH 713198

- Python Durga Software Solutions
- Django Durga Software Solutions

CutShort Certified Python - Basic - CutShort

Issued Jul 2020 - Expires Jul 2021 15300

- Basic Python HackerRank 283ED448B149
- C (Basic) HackerRank
- C (Intermediate) HackerRank 53BBE0AC8C3B

Skills

Python • Java • Hadoop • Django • Core Java • Linux • Android • JavaScript • C (Programming Language) • HTML5